Today's goes to whatever kept Clarence Thomas from showing up to work on Monday.
Now, Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas was a no show for Monday's oral arguments and there was no reason given for his absence.
Oh, wow.
So whatever kept him away, let's just hope it keeps happening again and again forever, forever, ever, forever, ever.
So regardless, he needs to be distracted from making laws that will turn our lives into a Roots reboot.
You know, what would be crazy is that if that's really what happened and we came back to a Roots situation, they would put him in the field.
Like he thinks that it would be like, ha ha ha, I'm laughing at your Negroes.
You would be right out there in the field.
Like they do not like you, bro.
Our letdown goes to fake beauty standards.
Literally, soon models and influencers generated through AI will compete in a Miss AI beauty pageant.
They say, you know what?
We found a loophole in our quest to objectify women.
We could just like make them.
Ha ha.
So, you know, who needs social progress when you can have a digital catwalk of shame?
And what's funny and not funny at the same time is they're going to have a bunch of Black models in here that are going to be run by white people.
That's what's going to happen.
Remember, I said it.
We are, we are, we are.